fax.plus 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy - FAX.PLUS

Alohi SA (“FAX.PLUS”) recognizes that its customers, visitors and users, want to know what’s up with privacy. FAX.PLUS provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus), FAX.PLUS Software and/or the FAX.PLUS Service. If you do not agree to our practices, please do not use the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus), FAX.PLUS Software, or FAX.PLUS Service.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the FAX.PLUS Terms of Service. Your use of the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus), FAX.PLUS Software and the FAX.PLUS Service and any personal information you provide on the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus) or FAX.PLUS Service remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.

**WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?**  
This Privacy Policy is part of FAX.PLUS’s Terms of Service and covers the treatment of user information, including personally identifying information, obtained by FAX.PLUS, including information obtained when you access the FAX.PLUS’s Site, use the FAX.PLUS Service or any other software provided by FAX.PLUS.  
This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that FAX.PLUS does not own or control, or to individuals whom FAX.PLUS does not employ or manage.

**THE INFORMATION FAX.PLUS COLLECTS**  
FAX.PLUS may obtain the following types of information, which may include information that can be used to identify you as specified below (“Personally Identifying Information”):  
User Provided Information: You provide certain Personally Identifiable Information, such as your mobile phone number to FAX.PLUS when choosing to participate in various uses of the FAX.PLUS Service, such as registering as a user. In connection with your use of the Services.  
Log File Information: When you use the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus) or FAX.PLUS mobile application, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser or mobile app sends to our servers. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages and the date and time of your request.

**COOKIES**  
Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We (including service providers who are working on our behalf) use various technologies to collect information, which may include saving cookies to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us to improve the FAX.PLUS Services and your experience, customize your experience and preferences, allow you to access and use the FAX.PLUS Services without re-entering your username and/or password, understand which areas and features of the FAX.PLUS Services are most popular and count visits. We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”). Web beacons are electronic images (also called “gifs”) that may be used in the FAX.PLUS Services or in emails that help us to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon.  
Third party cookies: If you sign-up for, access, or log into the FAX.PLUS Services using third-party services, those third-party services may use cookies that are subject to those third-party services’ own rules and policies. FAX.PLUS does not control the use of cookies by such third-party services.

**THE INFORMATION FAX.PLUS DOES NOT COLLECT**  
FAX.PLUS does not collect emails, addresses or other contact information from its users’ mobile address book or contact lists other than name (first and last) and phone numbers.

**THE WAY FAX.PLUS USES INFORMATION**  
If you submit Personally Identifiable Information to us through the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus), or FAX.PLUS Service, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus) and FAX.PLUS Service. In particular, your mobile phone number is essential to your use of the FAX.PLUS Service and will be retained. We do not use your mobile phone number or other Personally Identifiable Information to send commercial or marketing messages.  
By signing up to FAX.PLUS you automatically subscribe to our newsletter to receive updates on new features and releases via email and/or mobile app push notifications. You may unsubscribe at any time using the unsubscribe link in the emails or turning off FAX.PLUS mobile app’s push notification service.

**WHEN FAX.PLUS DISCLOSES INFORMATION**  
We do not sell or share your Personally Identifiable Information (such as mobile phone number) with other third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use. We may collect and release Personally Identifiable Information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or to provide proof in case of a payment dispute or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with international law or respond to a court order, subpoena or equivalent.

**YOUR CHOICE**  
You may, of course, decline to submit Personally Identifiable Information through the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus) or the FAX.PLUS Service, in which case FAX.PLUS may not be able to provide certain services to you. If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy or Terms of Service, please delete your account, uninstall the FAX.PLUS mobile application and discontinue use of the FAX.PLUS Service; your continued usage of the FAX.PLUS Service will signify your assent to and acceptance of our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as SMS authentication in certain cases) to verify your identity before registering your mobile phone number and granting you access to the FAX.PLUS Service. Please contact FAX.PLUS via the available web forms with any questions about this Privacy Policy.

**THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS, LINKS TO OTHER SITES**  
We are not fans of advertising. FAX.PLUS is currently ad-free and we hope to keep it that way forever. We have no intention to introduce advertisement into the product, but if we ever do, will update this section.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY**  
FAX.PLUS uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to FAX.PLUS and you do so at your own risk. Using unsecured wifi or other unprotected networks to submit messages through the FAX.PLUS Service is never recommended. Once we receive your transmission of information, FAX.PLUS makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If FAX.PLUS learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN’S’ PRIVACY**  
Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, FAX.PLUS does not knowingly collect or maintain Personally Identifiable Information or non-personally-identifiable information on the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus) or FAX.PLUS Service from persons under 18 years of age, and no part of the FAX.PLUS Service is directed to or intended to be used by persons under 18. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use the FAX.PLUS Service or access the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus) at any time or in any manner. If FAX.PLUS learns that Personally Identifiable Information of persons under 18 years of age has been collected on the FAX.PLUS Site (www.fax.plus) or FAX.PLUS Service, then FAX.PLUS may deactivate the account and/or make the status submissions inaccessible.

**IN THE EVENT OF MERGER, SALE, OR BANKRUPTCY**  
In the event that is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

**CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE**  
This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the “effective date” below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Site (www.fax.plus) and Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any amendments.

Date Last Modified:  
This Privacy Policy was last modified October 10, 2018
